Kenneth Werner

Phone: 808-278-7317

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kenny-werner-20b8a91b7/

Itch.io: https://ahiddendev.itch.io/

GitHub: https://github.com/KennethWerner Artstation: https://www.artstation.com/austinjacob

Personal website: https://kennethwerner.github.io/portfolio/

Location: El Paso, Hawaii

A solo game developer currently looking for internships/entry level positions where I can apply my skills and bring value to my work environment. I am currently trying to build experience in today's high competition job market and move my way up into a successful career.

Skillset

Programming Languages: C#, Python, Lua, JSON, JavaScript, C++, HTML, CSS, MySQL

Information technology: SSH, Linux/Windows Server Environments, Office Suite, Windows RDC, Data recovery,

General Troubleshooting. Ethernet and Display system setups.

Game Engines: UnrealEngine 4, UnrealEngine 5, Unity3D, Roblox Studio,

Misc.: 3D modeling, Substance Painter, Character Rigging, Shader Creation, 3D Printing and Modeling, Adobe Suite, Google Suite, Google playstore publishing, ad integration.

Projects

Incremental Bee Farm Simulator—Google Play Store

Created Modular JSON systems from the ground up meant to be customizable for easy feature creation and data storage. Built Player interactable shops and Ad Integration.

HIDDEN— Itch.io Scored 2nd in Participating GameJam

Created state-machines, Networked Data Delivery, Customization features, and Client Lobby systems from the ground up using UnrealEngine4

Work Experience

Freelance Slack Chatbot Creator, Remote — Development and R&D

September 2019

Created a Slack Chatbot that would parse data from client's requested Excel File.

FacePainting in paradise, Honolulu, HI — Entertainment Specialist -reference given on Request

October 2015 - October 2022

Job required people skills, and handling client requests on a weekly basis with revisions regularly needed.

General IT Services and Consulting, Computer/printer repair. Promotional Media Designer.

AsylumCentral Servers, Remote — Administrator

September 2014 - February 2016

Helped manage and handle clients in a forum and virtual environment.

Created Administration Tools in Lua.

Education

StraighterLine Edu, Online

September 2019 - April 2021

Cultural Anthropology, United States History, Biology 101, Chemistry, General Physics, Information Technology, College Algebra, Algebra 101.

Homeschooled

September 2005 - April 2017